LINDA VAUGHAN

8214 80th Dr NE Marysville, WA 98270

<u>LVaughan226@gmail.com</u> (831) 236-0729-cell

SUMMARY

Highly motivated, dependable, experienced professional with expertise in accounting, administrative, and procurement roles. Extensive experience with multiple departments in client care and customer service. Works well under pressure with the ability to multi-task. Team player as well as working independently under minimal supervision.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Comprehensive knowledge of the process and procedures of handling administrative tasks.
- In-depth knowledge of basic accounting and bookkeeping.
- Ability to take initiative and work well with a team as well as working independently.
- Possess good time management, strong organizational, multitasking and customer service skills.
- Close attention to detail. Good decision making with positive attitude.
- Good written and verbal communication skills and work effectively in a team environment.
- Ability to work under tight deadlines.
- Skilled with Internet knowledge and computer programs, such as Microsoft Word, Excel, Access, Power Point, Outlook, Teams, Adobe Acrobat, Lawson, Kronos, MediTract, Insight, Helpstar, AppFolio, TOPS, Toggl, NetCapture, DocuWare and Quicken.
- Knowledge of office equipment such as 10-key, copiers, fax, scanners, printers and check signer.

EXPERIENCE

PUGET SOUND GUARDIANS

2017-present

Financial Assistant

- Assist Financial Associates and Care Coordinators with various client accounting and guardianship related research or personal needs.
- Compose and submit notifications of legal guardianship or legal documents to government agencies (Social Security, Dept. of Social Services, Veterans Admin.) pension, insurance, banks/investment and utility companies.
- Reconcile monthly bank and investment statements.
- Produce bank reconciliation, check registers or other financial reports.
- Maintain client files and archive as required.
- Assist in preparing court reports.
- Assist with gathering tax transcripts and tax filing documents.

WPI REAL ESTATE

2014-2017

C.A.M. Bookkeeper/Coordinator/Receptionist

- A/R-Receive, post, scan checks, deposit HOA dues, escrow funds, insurance and other receivables.
- A/P-Code vendor invoices and other HOA related payments. Post/ prepare checks.
- Order coupon books and statements for homeowners.
- Manage and prepare homeowner delinquency letters and reports. Send accounts to collections.
- Assist homeowners with account questions.
- Set up homeowner accounts and various files.
- Assistant and support for Community Association Property Managers and Accounting Staff.
- Scheduled and assisted with interviews for potential employees.
- Obtain maintenance bids and other requests for HOA properties.
- Send out homeowner notices, welcome packets and other documents to HOAs. Maintain files.
- Open office for business day.
- Answer heavy phone calls from tenants, homeowners, banks and vendors.
- Receive/open mail, sort/distribute invoices and checks to accountants/property managers.
- Greet the public as they come in for meetings, collect rent payments and assist with general questions.
- Run mail through postage meters, send faxes, scan lease documents, etc. and insert into tenants files in AppFolio and TOPS.
- Run meter and copier reports then send information to accountants for billing.
- Update NWMLS and CondoCerts Websites.

.

COMMUNITY HOSPITAL OF THE MONTEREY PENINSULA (AKA CHOMP) 1984-2014

Administrative Specialist-Health Information Technology Dept.

1996-2014

- Assistant to the CIO.
- Responsible for providing budget formulation, financial management and reporting of over \$10 million capital equipment purchases and ongoing technology project budgets.
- Served as a liaison between project teams and managers.
- Assisted in reviewing project issues and implementing resolutions to meet timeline productivity, quality and goals.
- Performed tasks of monitoring department's annual \$20 million budget finances and preparing status reports.
- Provided accurate information and advice to CIO on department budgetary and finance issues. Prepared monthly and yearly financial expense reports.
- Negotiated and procured all computer related equipment and software for the hospital and its subsidiaries. Maintained databases with serial numbers and warranty information.

- Responsible for proper accounting of purchase orders, receiving, coding and invoices.
- Managed all hardware/ software contracts, leases, maintenance, and license agreements.
- Scanned contracts and monitored renewal dates.
- Performed other general clerical duties such ordering supplies, filing, scanning and answering phones as requested in a timely manner.

Office Systems Tech-**Financial Services** 1984-1996

- Assistant to the CFO.
- Performed clerical duties for the Finance Department. Successfully compiled and presented reports.
- Served as Property Management for hospital owned Professional Center.
- Managed budget reports.
- Tracked coding of expenses for all cost centers.
- Responsible for accurate cash receivables and patient accounts.
- Assistant to the Reimbursement Coordinator. Responsible for tracking proper DRG coding.
- Accounts Payable Clerk.

EDUCATION

UC Santa Cruz Monterey, CA

- Introduction to the Legal System
- Legal Writing
- Introduction to Legal Terminology

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Department Team Player Recipient.
- Top 10 nominee for Employee of the Year 2009 Award (out of 2,000 employees).
- Employee Award Recipient for providing substantial cost savings.
- Promoted multiple times reporting to Director level positions.

References upon request